export default [
    {
        'id': 1,
        'title': 'Hàng a-> o',
        'content': [
            {
                'question': 'あ',
                'answer': 'a'
            },
            {
                'question': 'い',
                'answer': 'i'
            },
            {
                'question': 'う',
                'answer': 'u'
            },
            {
                'question': 'え',
                'answer': 'e'
            },
            {
                'question': 'お',
                'answer': 'o'
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        'id': 2,
        'title': 'Hàng ka-> ki',
        'content': [
            {
                'question': 'か',
                'answer': 'ka'
            },
            {
                'question': 'き',
                'answer': 'ki'
            },
            {
                'question': 'く',
                'answer': 'ku'
            },
            {
                'question': 'け',
                'answer': 'ke'
            },
            {
                'question': 'こ',
                'answer': 'ko'
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        'id': 3,
        'title': 'Hàng sa-> so',
        'content': [
            {
                'question': 'さ',
                'answer': 'sa'
            },
            {
                'question': 'し',
                'answer': 'shi'
            },
            {
                'question': 'す',
                'answer': 'su'
            },
            {
                'question': 'せ',
                'answer': 'se'
            },
            {
                'question': 'そ',
                'answer': 'so'
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        'id': 4,
        'title': 'Hàng ta-> to',
        'content': [
            {
                'question': 'た',
                'answer': 'ta'
            },
            {
                'question': 'ち',
                'answer': 'chi'
            },
            {
                'question': 'つ',
                'answer': 'tsu'
            },
            {
                'question': 'て',
                'answer': 'te'
            },
            {
                'question': 'と',
                'answer': 'to'
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        'id': 5,
        'title': 'Toàn bộ hiragana',
        'content': [
            {
                'question': 'あ',
                'answer': 'a'
            },
            {
                'question': 'い',
                'answer': 'i'
            },
            {
                'question': 'う',
                'answer': 'u'
            },
            {
                'question': 'え',
                'answer': 'e'
            },
            {
                'question': 'お',
                'answer': 'o'
            },
            {
                'question': 'か',
                'answer': 'ka'
            },
            {
                'question': 'き',
                'answer': 'ki'
            },
            {
                'question': 'く',
                'answer': 'ku'
            },
            {
                'question': 'け',
                'answer': 'ke'
            },
            {
                'question': 'こ',
                'answer': 'ko'
            },
            {
                'question': 'さ',
                'answer': 'sa'
            },
            {
                'question': 'し',
                'answer': 'shi'
            },
            {
                'question': 'す',
                'answer': 'su'
            },
            {
                'question': 'せ',
                'answer': 'se'
            },
            {
                'question': 'そ',
                'answer': 'so'
            },
            {
                'question': 'た',
                'answer': 'ta'
            },
            {
                'question': 'ち',
                'answer': 'chi'
            },
            {
                'question': 'つ',
                'answer': 'tsu'
            },
            {
                'question': 'て',
                'answer': 'te'
            },
            {
                'question': 'と',
                'answer': 'to'
            },
        ]
    }
]
